freegames.ws 2016-10-30

# Computer Games at freegames.ws - Play online arcade, board, puzzles, 3D car games for free

**Personal Information Collected Online**  
  
Providing us with any personal information is not a requirement to access our site. We collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, we collect and store certain information automatically. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website.

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

The Internet domain of your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or institution you use to connect and access our site (company.com, institution.org, school.edu, etc.).  
Your IP address, which is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are connected to the Internet.  
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site.   
The date and time you access our site.   
The pages you visit.   
If you linked to our website from another website, the URL address of that website. 

We use the collected information for statistical and demographic purposes, i.e.: To count the number of visitors to our site, to establish the type of visitors, to list the most visited content, etc., all of these to improve and make our site more useful to visitors like you.  
  
**How Your Information May Be Shared**  
  
If You Send Us E-mail You may choose to provide us with personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request.

Unless you consent, we will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to reply to inquiries, handle complaints, provide operational notices and in program record-keeping.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share e-mail information with any other outside organizations.  
  
**Computer Tracking and Cookies**  
  
We do not use cookies currently; for your information:

Cookies are small pieces of electronic information, which a web site can store on a visitors hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies are very widely used on the Internet, and on many large company sites they are commonplace. No other web site can use or view the cookie set by a specific site.

Cookies help create a speedy web experience by remembering your address and email information, so you don't have to re-type it when making multiple purchases. They also enable you to recall previous purchases.

Cookies do not store credit card information.  
  
**Links**  
  
Freegames.ws regularly creates links to the web sites of other parties; we make every effort to link only to sites that carry the same standards of maintaining privacy of users. These pages may however link to other sites that do not meet our requirements. We cannot be held responsible for any material on sites other than that on Freegames.ws, whether we link to them or are linked from them, or any links they may provide.

When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.   
  
**Advertising**  
Third Party Advertising  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here = http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

For more information about advertising, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please contact the respective advertiser. 

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.   
  
**Liability**  
Freegames.ws makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, funcionality, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website. 

No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.

We will post any changes to our privacy policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

Reference in this website to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Freegames.ws
